http://www.payrollcompany.biz/company/payroll-company-overview/privacy/

VIEW ALL LOGINS
SolutionsHuman Capital Management SoftwarePayrollCulture and EngagementHRISBenefits and ACATime and AttendanceEmployee Self-Service (ESS)Performance ManagementOnboardingiSolved GO MobileTalent AcquisitionLearning Management System (LMS)TPC Human Resources401k AdministrationAdditional ProductsFSA & COBRACarrier FeedsBackground SearchesTax Credit ProcessingWorkers’ Compensation InsurancePaycardsResourcesYear-End ResourcesCOVID-19 ResourcesTPC BlogForms and DocumentsTPC Communications ArchiveCompanyTPC OverviewTPC HCMTPC HRTPC 401(k)Leadership TeamCareersContact UsRequest Information
HomeCompanyTPC OverviewPrivacy
The Payroll Company, Inc. Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices of The Payroll Company, Inc., and www.payrollcompany.biz. Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
It is The Payroll Company, Inc.’s responsibility to guard the individually identifiable information and other nonpublic personal or financial information (“Confidential Information”) of our clients, consumers, brokers and participants (“Stakeholders”) from any unauthorized access or use. We take this responsibility seriously and promise to all Stakeholders that The Payroll Company, Inc. does not and will not knowingly distribute, sell or otherwise transfer any Confidential Information for any reason, except as required by law or contract.
Except as otherwise described in this notice, we restrict access to Confidential Information about you to employees of our firm and other parties who must use that information to provide services to you. Their right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our firm, applicable law, and nondisclosure agreements where appropriate. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via e-mail in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect Confidential Information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. You can verify the authenticity of the security certificate at any time using your browser. In addition, access to your online account is always protected by a unique User ID and password of your choice.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations to guard your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration or premature destruction.
How can you protect your information?
There are three simple things you can do:
Do not share any unique User ID or password with any other individual.
Do not leave your unique User ID or password out in the open or in an insecure location.
When you have finished your task, always sign out immediately and close your browser.
Your Access and Control Regarding Your Information
Contact us in order to do any of the following:
Change/correct any data we have about you.
See what data we have about you, if any.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
The Payroll Company, Inc. offers you the ability to correct or change the information you submitted as often as necessary. Our contact info can be found at http://www.payrollcompany.biz/contact-us/
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Download The Payroll Company Privacy Policy.
CompanyTPC OverviewTPC HCMTPC HRTPC 401(k)Leadership TeamCareersContact Us
SOLUTIONSHuman Capital Management SoftwareTPC Human Resources401k AdministrationAdditional Products
RESOURCESTPC BlogAffordable Care Act ComplianceTPC Communications Archive
COMPANYTPC OverviewTPC HCMTPC HRTPC 401(k)Leadership TeamCareersContact Us
REQUEST INFORMATION
HomeiSolved LoginUser LoginsDEMOContact UsRequest InformationBlogSolutionsHuman Capital Management SoftwarePayrollCulture and EngagementHRISEmployee Benefits Administration Software and ACA ComplianceTime and AttendanceEmployee Self-Service (ESS)Performance ManagementOnboardingiSolved GO MobileTalent Acquisition401k AdministrationTPC Human ResourcesAdditional ProductsFSA and COBRACarrier FeedsBackground SearchesTax Credit ProcessingWorkers’ Compensation InsuranceResourcesYear-End ResourcesCOVID-19 ResourcesTPC Communications ArchiveCompanyTPC OverviewTPC HCMTPC HRTPC 401(k)TPC StaffingLeadership TeamCareers
